Stay peculiar.
Miss Peregrine's Home for Peculiar Children is a fantasy,
adventure, drama film directed by Tim Burton.
A teenager finds himself transported to an island where he must help protect a group of
orphans with special powers from creatures intent on destroying them.
Miss Peregrine, played by Eva Green.
Jacob Portman, played by Asa Butterfield.
Barron, played by Samuel L. Jackson.
Miss Avocet, played by Judi Dench.
Ornithologist, played by Rupert Everett.
Franklin Portman, played by Chris O'Dowd.
Miss Peregrine's Home for Peculiar Children is a 2016 dark fantasy film directed by Tim
Burton and written by Jane Goldman, based on the 2011 novel by Ransom Riggs.
The film stars Eva Green, Asa Butterfield, Chris O'Dowd, Allison Janney, Rupert
Everett, Terence Stamp, Ella Purnell, Judi Dench, and Samuel L.
Filming began in February 2015 in London and the Tampa Bay Area.
The film premiered at Fantastic Fest in Austin, Texas, on September 25, 2016, and was
theatrically released in the United States on September 30, 2016, by 20th Century Fox.
It received mixed to positive reviews, with praise for Burton's
direction and visual atmosphere, but criticism for its plot.
It grossed $296.5 million worldwide against a production budget of $110 million.
The film explores themes of wales, children's home,
shapeshifting, falcon, time travel.
The tone is emotional.